# RASHEED BASHA SHAIK

# **Quality specialist 1**

**9704805497** 

@ rasheedbasha11.shaik@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shaikrashid-basha-9568b5195/

Pangalore, India

#### **SUMMARY**

Skilled quality specialist associate and 1.7 year of professional experience in working with key stakeholders and liaising between technical and managerial levels.

To work in a healthy and challenging environment and be associated with a progressive organization, where I can update and contribute my knowledge for the growth of the organization.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### 07/2021 - 07/2022

# Quality specialist 1

Hyderabad

#### **Amazon development center**

**Company Description** 

- · Worked in a collaborative environment and contribute to the growth of the respective team/program.
- · Meet business metrics and goals. i.e. SLA, productivity, quality and utilization benchmarks.
- · Understanding performance metrics for driving business goals.
- Identifying patterns emerging in the audits and contribute to process/program improvements.
- · Provided inputs on new metrics and tools. Come up with suggestions to improve productivity and quality.
- Follow Standard Operating Procedures(SOPs) to perform manual audits and resolve outliers.

## 05/2020 - 02/2021

# Data labeling analyst

### Banaglore

**Unbxd inc**Company Description

- Develop and manage data that supports relevancy or performance improvements.
- Review key aspects of feed catalog to evaluate the factors/fields driving results.
- · Analyze the performance failures and suggesting fixing.
- Creating a detail business analysis, outline problems, opportunities and solutions for a business.
- Performing Variance analysis.
- · Gathering information about problems to be solved or procedures to be improved.
- Formulating ways for business to improve, based on previous research. Presenting findings to decision makers.
- Interpret and Analyze data to understand business performance for driving a business solution of an ecommerce industry.

#### **EDUCATION**

07/2014 - 04/2019

B. Tech : CGPA- 6.07

G Pulla reddy engineering college

07/2011 - 03/2013

Internediate education: Percentage- 84.8

Narayana junior college

07/2010 - 03/2011

Secondary school eduaction: Percentage- 73.6

Sri sudha high school

# **SKILLS**

Tabelau Python MySQL Google analytics Data analytics and lebeling Data audit Ms excel

# **LANGUAGES**

English Proficient



Hindi Proficient



Telugu Proficient

